export const levels = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is 5 + 3?",
    answer: "8",
    reward: 10,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which city is known as the Big Apple?",
    answer: "New York",
    reward: 15,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "A man was found murdered in a room. The only clue is a calendar with 6, 4, 9, and 10 circled. Who is the killer?",
    answer: "June",
    reward: 20,
  },
  // {
  //   id: 4,
  //   question: "A gangster is found dead with '710 57735' written near him. What does it mean when flipped upside down?",
  //   answer: "Elles",
  //   reward: 25,
  // },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "I walk in the shadows, feared by many. I take life without a trace. What am I?",
    answer: "Hitman",
    reward: 30,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "A mob boss is shot in his study. A bloody playing card, the Ace of Spades, is found. Who is the killer?",
    answer: "Lawyer",
    reward: 35,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "A thief is escaping and finds three doors: one with a sniper, one with hungry wolves, and one with fire. Which door is safest?",
    answer: "Fire",
    reward: 40,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "A detective is murdered. The clue is a paper with 3, 14, 15, 92 written on it. Who is the suspect?",
    answer: "Teacher",
    reward: 45,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "A stolen diamond is hidden in plain sight but never seen. Where is it?",
    answer: "Ice",
    reward: 50,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "A hitman leaves a note: 'Iâ€™ll see you at 12:15, where the queen rests.' Where is the target?",
    answer: "Cemetery",
    reward: 55,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "A man is found dead in an alley with a matchstick nearby. What was he?",
    answer: "Gambler",
    reward: 60,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Three men drink the same poison. Only one dies. How?",
    answer: "Ice",
    reward: 65,
  },
];
